Christmas Encore is a romance, drama, tv movie film directed by Bradley Walsh.
A struggling actress is cast in her last off (off) Broadway show - a modern take on
“A Christmas Carol” - before giving up her dream and moving home.
Instead, she finds romance with her director and a
renewed passion for her craft and the city.
But when the historic theater loses its lease and the show is set to fold,
she and her cast mates are need of a Christmas miracle.
Charlotte Lacy, played by Maggie Lawson.
Julian Walker, played by Brennan Elliott.
Sid, played by Art Hindle.
Franny Forman, played by Tracey Hoyt.
Naomi, played by Mercedes de la Zerda.
Brady, played by Mika Amonsen.
This is a list of television films produced for the cable networks
Hallmark Channel (HC) and Hallmark Mystery (HMM).
Such films are currently called Hallmark Channel
Original Movies and Hallmark Mysteries.
The Hallmark Channel was officially launched in August 2001, with its sister channel Hallmark
Movies & Mysteries (originally Hallmark Movie Channel) launched in January 2004.
In addition to stand-alone original films, both channels broadcast a number of original film series, including Garage Sale Mysteries, Jesse
Stone, Signed, Sealed, Delivered, Aurora Teagarden Mysteries and The Good Witch, as well having produced mystery-themed wheel series.
The Hallmark Channel achieved its highest-ever broadcast premiere ratings with the 2014 original movie
Christmas Under Wraps, starring Candace Cameron Bure, which was watched by 5.8 million viewers.
Both networks receive their highest ratings during their "Countdown to Christmas" period, with a
succession of festive original films being broadcast from late October to late December.
A number of these films are also carried in Canada by the W Network and Citytv under content distribution agreements with Hallmark parent
Crown Media; the vast majority of Hallmark Channel films are filmed in Canada and thus qualify for Canadian content quotas.
In the United Kingdom, Hallmark Original Movies are
shown on Movies 24, a sister channel.
The film explores themes of theater play, struggling actor, christmas.
The tone is emotional.